

Maloth Saikumar video editor, video grapher

C

9640985461,9949627522

 \square

Saik47379@gmail.com



VIRALBOOST2024



Experience

 Naresh IT Technologies videographer & video editor January 2024 - Present

• Commando kennels video creator & video editor December 2022 - October 2023

freelancer

Video editor February2020 - November 2022

Education

- Bachelor of Science 2020
- Bachlore Degree Clinical Nutrition
- Dietetics Department SLG Hospital
- Osmania University

Skills

- Camera operation and handling
- · Lighting and sound design
- Storytelling and visual narrative
- Colour Grading & sound design
- Effects & Transitions
- · Creativity & Keyframing
- Communication Skills
- English
- Hindi
- Telugu

About me

I am saikumar Video Editor and videographer 3+ years experience of video editing success. Talent in assembling rawfootage, reordering sequences and adjusting content to align with artistic vision. Aiming to leverage strong proficiency in Software to add value to projects. Creative Video Editor bringing 3+ years of comprehensive experience editing film and video.